const Data = [
    {
      "id":1,
      "question":"1.Explain JDK, JRE and JVM?",
      "answer1":"answer-a",
      "answer2":"answer-b",
      "answer3":"answer-c",
      "answer4":"answer-d",
      "correct-answer":"answer-b"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question":"2.Explain public static void main(String args[]) in Java?",
        "answer1":"answer-a",
        "answer2":"answer-b",
        "answer3":"answer-c",
        "answer4":"answer-d",
        "correct-answer":"answer-c"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "question":"3.Why Java is platform independent?",
        "answer1":"answer-a",
        "answer2":"answer-b",
        "answer3":"answer-c",
        "answer4":"answer-d",
        "correct-answer":"answer-a"
      },
      {
        "id":4,
        "question":"4.Why Java is not 100% Object-oriented?",
        "answer1":"answer-a",
        "answer2":"answer-b",
        "answer3":"answer-c",
        "answer4":"answer-d",
        "correct-answer":"answer-d"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "question":"5.What are wrapper classes in Java?",
        "answer1":"answer-a",
        "answer2":"answer-b",
        "answer3":"answer-c",
        "answer4":"answer-d",
        "correct-answer":"answer-b"
      },
      // {
      //   "id":6,
      //   "question":"question6",
      //   "answer1":"answer-a",
      //   "answer2":"answer-b",
      //   "answer3":"answer-c",
      //   "answer4":"answer-d",
      //   "correct-answer":"answer-b"
      // },
      // {
      //   "id":7,
      //   "question":"question7",
      //   "answer1":"answer-a",
      //   "answer2":"answer-b",
      //   "answer3":"answer-c",
      //   "answer4":"answer-d",
      //   "correct-answer":"answer-c"
      // },
      // {
      //   "id":8,
      //   "question":"question8",
      //   "answer1":"answer-a",
      //   "answer2":"answer-b",
      //   "answer3":"answer-c",
      //   "answer4":"answer-d",
      //   "correct-answer":"answer-d"
      // },
      // {
      //   "id":9,
      //   "question":"question9",
      //   "answer1":"answer-a",
      //   "answer2":"answer-b",
      //   "answer3":"answer-c",
      //   "answer4":"answer-d",
      //   "correct-answer":"answer-b"
      // },
      // {
      //   "id":10,
      //   "question":"question10",
      //   "answer1":"answer-a",
      //   "answer2":"answer-b",
      //   "answer3":"answer-c",
      //   "answer4":"answer-d",
      //   "correct-answer":"answer-a"
      // }
]

module.exports=Data